<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Demo</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use">Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="notice_terms_of_use">
        Thank you for enrolling in trainings with CodePlay Studio.\n
        \nThis app is developed for training purpose used in Android Development training conducted
        by CodePlay Studio, lisenced under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); You may
        not use this app except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License
        at\n\n\t\t\thttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
        \n\nThe source code is provided "AS IS". Any expressed or implied warranties, including,
        but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular
        purpose are disclaimed. In no event shall the copyright holder be liable for any direct,
        indirect, incidental, special, exemplary, or consequential damages (Including, but not limited to,
        procurement of goods or services; loss of use, data, or profits; or business interruption)
        however caused and on any theory of liability, whether in contract, strict liability, or tort
        (Including negligence or otherwise) arising in any way out of the use of this source code,
        even if advised of the possibility of such damage.
        \n\nRedistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification,
        are permitted provided that the above copyright notice and disclaimer are retained in the
        redistributions of source code or reproduced in the documentation and/or other materials provided
        with the redistributions in binary form.
    </string>
    <string name="copyright">Copyright &#169; 2017 CodePlay Studio. %s</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="widgets">Widgets (Views)</string>
    <string-array name="spinner_items">
        <item>item 1</item>
        <item>item 2</item>
        <item>item 3</item>
        <item>item 4</item>
        <item>item 5</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="layouts">Layouts (ViewGroups)</string>
    <string name="framelayout">FrameLayout</string>
    <string name="framelayout_short_desc">A layout designed to block out an area on the screen.</string>
    <string name="relativelayout">RelativeLayout</string>
    <string name="relativelayout_short_desc">A layout where the position of the childrens can be described in relation to each other or to the parent.</string>
    <string name="linearlayout">LinearLayout</string>
    <string name="linearlayout_short_desc">A layout to display its children in a single order (horizontal or vertical).</string>
    <string name="scrollview">ScrollView</string>
    <string name="scrollview_short_desc">A layout that allows the view hierarchy placed within it to be scrolled when the hierarchy is beyond its own bound.</string>
    <string name="gridlayout">GridLayout (API 14)</string>
    <string name="gridlayout_short_desc">A layout that places its childrens in rectangular grid.</string>
    <string name="coordinatorlayout">CoordinatorLayout (API 21)</string>
    <string name="coordinatorlayout_short_desc">A layout that manages interactions between its children.</string>
    <string name="coordinator_article">Android is a mobile operating system (OS) currently developed by Google,
        based on the Linux kernel and designed primarily for touchscreen mobile devices
        such as smartphones and tablets.
        \n\nAndroid was initially authored by Android, Inc., which Google bought in 2005,[17]
        and unveiled it in 2007, along with the founding of the Open Handset Alliance –
        a consortium of hardware, software, and telecommunication companies devoted to
        advancing open standards for mobile devices.
        \n\nAndroid\'s source code is released by Google under open source licenses,
        although most Android devices ultimately ship with both open source and proprietary software,
        including required proprietary components for Google\'s services.
    </string>
    <string name="tablayout">Tab Layout</string>
    <string name="tablayout_desc_short">A horizontal layout to display tabs.</string>
    <string name="viewflipper">ViewFlipper</string>
    <string name="viewflipper_short_desc">A layout that animates between two or more views.</string>
    <string name="listview">ListView</string>
    <string name="listview_short_desc">A layout displays a list of scrollable items vertically.</string>
    <string name="gridview">GridView</string>
    <string name="gridview_short_desc">A layout displays items in two-dimensional scrollable grid.</string>
    <string name="recyclerview">RecyclerView (API 21)</string>
    <string name="recyclerview_short_desc">A more advanced and flexible ListView/GridView designed for displaying large data sets efficiently.</string>
</resources>
